I was already in the works trying to develop this app for two years.
They took over and within three weeks my app was launched.
I've worked with several providers in the past and the result has been terrible.
This is the first time that I've worked with two people that go above and beyond for you.
And Omer has simplified everything, created great handover notes for me and got the whole thing ticking along really well. The whole project with Zia was amazing.
The outcome that was promised was delivered.
So his after sales support continues to this day.
I will be definitely working with him again in the future.
Omer and Zia are who you have to work with.
I highly recommend Zia and his team at Zumetrix.